http://www.jrk.com/cookie-policy/

Your Rights and Choices
The CCPA provide consumers (California residents) with specific rights regarding their personal information. This section describes your CCPA rights and explains how to exercise those rights.
Access to Specific Information and Data Portability Rights
You have the right to request that JRK Property Holdings disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights), we will disclose to you:
The categories of personal information we collected about you.The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you.Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information.The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information.The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you (also called a data portability request).If we sold or disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, two separate lists disclosing:sales, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient purchased; anddisclosures for a business purpose, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient obtained.
Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights
To Exercise access, data portability, and deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us by either:
Calling us at 310-268-8344 and asking for our CCPA department.Emailing us at CCPA@JRK.com
Only you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. You may also make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. The verifiable consumer request must:
Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collect personal information or an authorized representative.Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.
We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you.
Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us. However, we do consider requests made through your password protected account sufficiently verified when the request relates to personal information associated with that specific account.
We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor’s identity or authority to make the request.
Non-Discrimination
We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not:
Deny you goods or services.Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate of goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.
Collection of Personal Information
JRK Property Holdings has collected the following categories of personal information from its consumers within the last twelve (12) months:
CategoryExamplesIdentifiers.A real name, alias, current and previous postal address(es), email address, phone number, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, account name, Social Security number, driver’s license number, passport number, current or past job history, or other similar identifiers.Commercial information.Records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.Usage.Information on the User’s interaction with JRK Residential Group and affiliated websites.Geolocation data.Physical location, generally.
We also collect personal information from other sources:
Information received as part of routine card verification (fraud) checks.Information received as part of routine credit checks.Information received as part of routine background checks.
Use of Personal Information
We may use or disclose the personal information we collect for one or more of the following business purposes:
To fulfill or meet the reason you provided the information. For example, if you share your name and contact information to request a price quote or ask a question about our products or services, we will use that personal information to respond to your inquiry. If you provide your personal information to purchase a product or service, we will use that information to process your payment and facilitate delivery. We may also save your information to facilitate new product orders or process returns.To provide, support, personalize, and develop our Websites, products, and services.To create, maintain, customize, and secure your accounts with us.To process your requests, purchases, transactions, and payments and prevent transactional fraud.To provide you with support and respond to your inquiries, including to investigate and address your concerns and monitor and improve our responses
Sale of Personal Information
In the preceding twelve (12) months, JRK Property Holdings has sold the following categories of personal information:
CategorySoldCategory A: Identifiers.NoCategory B: California Customer Records Personal Information categories.NoCategory C: Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law.NoCategory D: Commercial Information.No
Service Providers
We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including hosting and maintenance, error monitoring, debugging, performance monitoring, billing, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We may share your Personal Information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services. We also require these third parties to maintain the privacy and security of the Personal Information they process on our behalf.
Our Story
Our Properties
Join Our Team
Contact Us
Corporate Headquarters: 11766 Wilshire Blvd., 15th Floor | Los Angeles, CA 90025
Phone: (310) 268-8344 | Fax: (310) 268-7943 | Residential Relations Line: (310) 696-7363
Copyright © 2020 JRK Property Holdings. All Rights Reserved
Privacy Policy
Privacy & Cookie Policy
This website, based in the United States, uses "cookies" to enhance your browsing experience and to allow us to improve our website usefulness to you and to us. Learn more about cookies and how to change your consents in our Privacy and Cookie Policies.Accept
